<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Chat Arxiv cs.GR</title><link>https://github.com/qhduan/cn-chat-arxiv</link><description>This is arxiv RSS feed for cs.GR</description><item><title>Holo-VQVAE&#26159;&#19968;&#31181;&#38024;&#23545;&#20165;&#30456;&#20301;&#20840;&#24687;&#22270;&#30340;&#26032;&#22411;&#29983;&#25104;&#26694;&#26550;&#65292;&#32467;&#21512;&#20102;&#30690;&#37327;&#37327;&#21270;&#21464;&#20998;&#33258;&#21160;&#32534;&#30721;&#22120;&#30340;&#32467;&#26500;&#65292;&#36890;&#36807;&#38598;&#25104;&#35282;&#35889;&#26041;&#27861;&#26469;&#23398;&#20064;&#22270;&#20687;&#22495;&#65292;&#22312;&#20840;&#24687;&#22270;&#29983;&#25104;&#20013;&#23454;&#29616;&#20102;&#20174;&#22797;&#26434;&#20998;&#24067;&#20013;&#30452;&#25509;&#29983;&#25104;&#22810;&#26679;&#21270;&#20840;&#24687;&#20869;&#23481;&#12290;</title><link>https://arxiv.org/abs/2404.01330</link><description>&lt;p&gt;
Holo-VQVAE&#65306;&#29992;&#20110;&#20165;&#30456;&#20301;&#20840;&#24687;&#22270;&#30340;VQ-VAE
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Holo-VQVAE: VQ-VAE for phase-only holograms
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
https://arxiv.org/abs/2404.01330
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Holo-VQVAE&#26159;&#19968;&#31181;&#38024;&#23545;&#20165;&#30456;&#20301;&#20840;&#24687;&#22270;&#30340;&#26032;&#22411;&#29983;&#25104;&#26694;&#26550;&#65292;&#32467;&#21512;&#20102;&#30690;&#37327;&#37327;&#21270;&#21464;&#20998;&#33258;&#21160;&#32534;&#30721;&#22120;&#30340;&#32467;&#26500;&#65292;&#36890;&#36807;&#38598;&#25104;&#35282;&#35889;&#26041;&#27861;&#26469;&#23398;&#20064;&#22270;&#20687;&#22495;&#65292;&#22312;&#20840;&#24687;&#22270;&#29983;&#25104;&#20013;&#23454;&#29616;&#20102;&#20174;&#22797;&#26434;&#20998;&#24067;&#20013;&#30452;&#25509;&#29983;&#25104;&#22810;&#26679;&#21270;&#20840;&#24687;&#20869;&#23481;&#12290;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Holography stands at the forefront of visual technology innovation, offering immersive, three-dimensional visualizations through the manipulation of light wave amplitude and phase. Contemporary research in hologram generation has predominantly focused on image-to-hologram conversion, producing holograms from existing images. These approaches, while effective, inherently limit the scope of innovation and creativity in hologram generation. In response to this limitation, we present Holo-VQVAE, a novel generative framework tailored for phase-only holograms (POHs). Holo-VQVAE leverages the architecture of Vector Quantized Variational AutoEncoders, enabling it to learn the complex distributions of POHs. Furthermore, it integrates the Angular Spectrum Method into the training process, facilitating learning in the image domain. This framework allows for the generation of unseen, diverse holographic content directly from its intricately learned distributions.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
arXiv:2404.01330v1 Announce Type: cross  Abstract: Holography stands at the forefront of visual technology innovation, offering immersive, three-dimensional visualizations through the manipulation of light wave amplitude and phase. Contemporary research in hologram generation has predominantly focused on image-to-hologram conversion, producing holograms from existing images. These approaches, while effective, inherently limit the scope of innovation and creativity in hologram generation. In response to this limitation, we present Holo-VQVAE, a novel generative framework tailored for phase-only holograms (POHs). Holo-VQVAE leverages the architecture of Vector Quantized Variational AutoEncoders, enabling it to learn the complex distributions of POHs. Furthermore, it integrates the Angular Spectrum Method into the training process, facilitating learning in the image domain. This framework allows for the generation of unseen, diverse holographic content directly from its intricately learne
&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>